{
    "subject": "resource/John_Cantwell_(general)",
    "predicate": "ontology/battle",
    "object": "resource/Iraq_War",
    "human_readable": "John Cantwell (general) was involved in the Iraq War.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.956571102142334,
            "question": "What role did John Cantwell play in the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9349988698959351,
            "question": "What impact did John Cantwell's involvement in the Iraq War have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9257763624191284,
            "question": "What war was John Cantwell involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9203999638557434,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or actions associated with John Cantwell during the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.878244161605835,
            "question": "What are some of the broader historical contexts surrounding the Iraq War that can be considered in relation to John Cantwell's involvement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8130334615707397,
            "question": "What sources can be consulted to learn more about John Cantwell and his role in the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7598227858543396,
            "question": "Is there any information available about John Cantwell's background or experiences before the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7500512599945068,
            "question": "Is there any information available about John Cantwell's life after the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7155441641807556,
            "question": "Are there any accounts or perspectives from other individuals who worked alongside John Cantwell during the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.711082398891449,
            "question": "Who was John Cantwell?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Cantwell (general) was involved in the Iraq War.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5155_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any accounts or perspectives from other individuals who worked alongside John Cantwell during the Iraq War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5155_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about John Cantwell's life after the Iraq War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5155_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about John Cantwell's background or experiences before the Iraq War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5155_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5155_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided support the triple that John Cantwell, a general, was involved in the Iraq War. The text explicitly states that he served as Director of Strategic Operations in Headquarters Multi National Forces Iraq in 2006 and later condemned the invasion and occupation of Iraq during an interview with the Australian Broadcasting Corporation."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that \"John Cantwell (general) was involved in the Iraq War.\" Specifically, the document mentions Brigadier General John Cantwell's deployment to Iraq in 2006 as the Director of Strategic Operations in Headquarters Multi National Forces Iraq and his subsequent promotion to Major General due to his service. Additionally, he is quoted denouncing the invasion of Iraq, indicating his involvement and perspective on the conflict."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}